Models.
Model.
Thanks for your time.
Which do you prefer, member color or all different colors of orange?
She wants to dye it herself.
I think I'd be happier with member color.
I don't see any orange.
I don't think so.
It makes me look good.
The shoes are nice.
Overall...
No belly?
I want her to have a belly or legs.
I wanted her to show her belly or her legs.
What's the setlist?
It's supposed to be a lot of cool
but the songs are supposed to be cool.
A lot of exposure.
Where is Can showing?
Skinny.
Tummy
Tummy.
about
tool
Thank you
please
pounding
Amazing.
Cute.
You said it was a long wrestling match.
When I first came out here alone.
I was too exposed.
I don't know.
It's so modern.
Cute. Cute.
Far beyond my imagination.
It exceeded my imagination
That's what I'm talking about.
That's why it's so delicate.
I thought so.
Because of the color scheme
It's a de type.
I'm looking forward to it.
I can't wait to wear it.
I'll lose weight.
Thanks for your hard work.
I can't wait to wear it.
It's so good
And the pants are falling down.
I can't believe I'm wearing this outfit at all.
At least when we're all together.
Dedede, dedede, dedede.
Woo.
LOL!
Is it nice?
Totally different from usual.
It's a different feeling.
I had her wear it.
Stylish.
My theme is stylish.
I want to play a lot of cool songs
I want to play a lot of cool songs.
But I may have never danced to a Gyanparee song
I may have never danced to
I'll do my best.
Three, two, one.
LOL!
LOL! LOL!
Laughter.
Model.
LOL!
LOL.
What do you guys look like?
LOL!
LOL.
This is self-explanatory.
what's going on?
LOL
LOL!
I was picturing in my head
The costumes and
And also this hair and makeup.
I had an image in my mind
I had an image in my mind, but
but I didn't have a specific idea of what I wanted.
I was very satisfied with the way they made it look just the way I wanted it.
Her eyes are sparkling!
Also, the wavy bangs and the waves.
I had my hair done in waves!
I think it's best to leave it to the professionals!
The main thing I wanted to wear was a jacket in the members' colors.
I love member-colored outfits!
I love member-colored outfits, so I had them put orange all over the jacket.
Also, the colors are all different, but they match each other perfectly.
It's colorful but not messy, but colorful.It's colorful, but not messy.
colorful but not messy.
and also, these boots are very difficult to make.
I also wondered if I could dance in these boots, which are difficult for me.
I'm not sure if I can dance in these boots.
but I wanted to make them stylish.
And also, I put my belly out!
I thought there are many people who love to show their stomachs for fun.
I thought many people love to show their belly for fun, so I made it a little bit sexy.
It's kind of feminine, but also cool and stylish.
I think there are a lot of them.
I like it a lot.
It's not too masculine and not too feminine.
I'm not too masculine and not too feminine.
I'm pretty much the same type of person in my own clothes.
That's what I asked him to do.
Here it is.
I recreated the outfit in my mind.
And the content of the live performance was pretty much the same.
I'm always making choreography for the group, so I was able to do it.
I'm always making choreography for the group.
I'm always making the choreography for the group, so I'd like to make the contents of the live possible.
Please lend me your help so that I can make it happen!
But you know, I don't like to battle in front of you.
I have a strong sense of kindness.
I mean...
My temper is strong, but...
I don't like to fight inside.
There are so many strangers.
I like fighting strangers.
But my friends are my friends.
I'm a team player.
Team friends.
They're more like family than friends.
That's right.
But I like to have fun.
I hope everyone ends up happy.
That's a funny story, isn't it? It's a lousy story, isn't it?
You think it's funny?
In the history of this project
Always?
Is it?